<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hip Hop School</string>
    <string name="history_text">The earliest hip hop music was performed live, at house parties and block party events, and it was not recorded. Prior to 1979, recorded hip hop music consisted mainly of PA system soundboard recordings of live party shows and early hip hop mixtapes by DJs. Puerto Rican DJ Disco Wiz is credited as the first hip hop DJ to create a \"mixed plate,\" or mixed dub recording, when, in 1977, he combined sound bites, special effects and paused beats to technically produce a sound recording. The first hip hop record is widely regarded to be The Sugarhill Gang\'s \"Rapper\'s Delight\", from 1979. It was the first hip hop record to gain widespread popularity in the mainstream and was where hip hop music got its name from (from the opening bar). However, much controversy surrounds this assertion as some regard the March 1979 single \"King Tim III (Personality Jock)\" by The Fatback Band, as a rap record. There are various other claimants for the title of first hip hop record.\
        \n
By the early 1980s, all the major elements and techniques of the hip hop genre were in place, and by 1982, the electronic (electro) sound had become the trend on the street and in dance clubs. New York City radio station WKTU featured Warp 9\'s \"Nunk,\" in a commercial to promote the station\'s signature sound of emerging hip hop[90] Though not yet mainstream, hip hop had begun to permeate the music scene outside of New York City; it could be found in cities as diverse as Los Angeles, Atlanta, Chicago, Washington, D.C., Baltimore, Dallas, Kansas City, San Antonio, Miami, Seattle, St. Louis, New Orleans, Houston, and Toronto. Indeed, \"Funk You Up\" (1979), the first hip hop record released by a female group, and the second single released by Sugar Hill Records, was performed by The Sequence, a group from Columbia, South Carolina which featured Angie Stone.[91] Despite the genre\'s growing popularity, Philadelphia was, for many years, the only city whose contributions could be compared to New York City\'s. Hip hop music became popular in Philadelphia in the late 1970s. The first released record was titled \"Rhythm Talk\", by Jocko Henderson.\
        \n
The New York Times had dubbed Philadelphia the \"Graffiti Capital of the World\" in 1971. Philadelphia native DJ Lady B recorded \"To the Beat Y\'All\" in 1979, and became the first female solo hip hop artist to record music. Schoolly D, starting in 1984 and also from Philadelphia, began creating a style that would later be known as gangsta rap.</string>
</resources>